(Bernadette:)- How are you?
- I'm amazing.
(Howard:)This is even better than I dreamed.
(Howard:)I look out the window...
(Howard:)...and it's all so unbelievable.
(Bernadette:)Good for you. I just had a seemingly
endless dinner with your mom.
Oh, yeah? That's nice. Heh.
(Bernadette:)It was. Until I found out you never told her
we're not gonna live with her.
(Bernadette:)Let's talk about that for a minute.
Hey, look, this pen is floating. Heh.
(Howard:)How crazy is that?
(Bernadette:)You said you told her but you never did.
(Howard:)Okay, okay, I know you're upset...
(Howard:)...but let me share something
I've learned since I got here.
(Howard:)You realize how small
your problems are...
(Howard:)...when you're looking down
on them from space.
Heh. Come on,
that's gotta make you feel better.
(Bernadette:)How clear is the image of me
on that screen?